Innocence isn't lost, it's stolen.
Eden is a thriller, drama, crime film directed by Megan Griffiths.
After a night out with friends, Hyun Jae accepts a late
night ride home from a young fire fighter.
What begins as a night of promise quickly turns into a nightmare when she is
abducted and imprisoned outside Las Vegas as a sex slave.
Eden / Hyun Jae, played by Jamie Chung.
Vaughan, played by Matt O'Leary.
Bob, played by Beau Bridges.
Priscilla, played by Jeanine Monterroza.
Svetlana, played by Naama Kates.
Mario, played by Eddie Martinez.
Eden is a 2024 American historical survival thriller film directed by Ron
Howard and written by Noah Pink, from a story by the pair.
It stars Jude Law, Ana de Armas, Vanessa Kirby, Sydney Sweeney, Daniel
Brühl, Felix Kammerer, Toby Wallace, and Richard Roxburgh.
The film is based on the true story of several European settlers, including Margret Wittmer, who arrive on the
isolated Floreana Island, in the Galápagos Islands, Ecuador, pre-World War II, hoping to start a life there.
The film premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival on September 7, 2024, and was released theatrically
in Germany on April 3, 2025, by Leonine, and in the United States by Vertical on August 22, 2025.
The film received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of escape, kidnapping,
killing, junkie, moral ambiguity.
The tone is emotional and intense.